Ajay
went to Wiki Option on Thursday in
preparation for this innings and amidst bad signals, the
back was published very poor numbers
due to which ICICI Lombard in the city red,
its staff choice numbers were weak
and reservation of independent directors in PTC India Financial Services,
saying this some serious governance loot so much
Mushaira due to which people in saliva tweeted,
JSW Energy numbers were worth watching
yesterday during the market closing from the front
but the numbers were from the shape of a
flower, like the father of the banks, that is why
set a look at these and like
wise you take care of the numbers, year after year
why the new looks better, but the meters
continue, that in the team,
after buying four of the suicide channel and only and only because
yesterday good, 10 percent of
scientific approach was released Infosys
because growth stock beating in Nasdaq and
Infosys is giving ID verification, city
state, fill in the text, good up idol, talk
well here yesterday from the old growing market,
job in the massive fund, which yesterday sold
more than four lakh shares automatically  Only the poor can
buy good wedding stocks. Now after that, if you can take a
last breath in green pet, then
come to Dimple.
You will find many red stocks here. L&T Infotech
results are difficult. According to the estimate of expenditure,
you have come here. The question is that
Kayan, who followed the estimates, can
say average of trees. The pharma
sector was very broken, hence the arrest of
Police Commissioner Mukesh. Tata Communications has
very poor numbers. Bajaj Auto's numbers are
very bad in app theft, but they are as per the
estimates, so subscribe.
Tejas Networks again has very weak numbers.
Oracle's numbers are very weak. It is a
very difficult time for BPCL, IOC, HPC. Unless you
take likes and when they will take them, it is
not known. The opposite is happening. The day it happens, there will be a
lot of loss. That is good news for this. It is
still around 88. And
ICC Bank ATR has closed for three slippers and sandals, so
Raktmoksha will be seen here too. Do it.
Ajay should
come. You have also seen these two,
Neeraj, the Chinese government residue here, the
player and Rajesh Bhaiya must have completed your scan here.  The
conviction rate
was both of them, in one
way, there is a very clear mandate here, there has been an
oath taken on the matter of robbery from here and it will be most
important for this, for this you can get 200
after that, it can be a little bit,
2009,
2013, 750, you can
achieve this very easily, so this is that
after a long time,
we were here a little soon, so the
biggest house out of this, bye bye see
you,
around 13 types of verses, today's puja should be
on the internet, I am on the switch of buy in one
like and selling his escape room,
remember, there is a pending sale, and if you
look here, it is hidden there,
one of the two teams is coming